Why are you so obsessed with my daughter?
Because she's done what you never could.
I'm going to make La Morte Bianca pay.
-Can we hear the plan first?
-Mikoy, we're out of time.
Should I wait until La Morte Bianca
sends me my parents' heads?
How did La Morte Bianca know
where we were?
How did she know where to send the box?
How else do you explain what happened?
Someone is feeding information
to the enemy.
Sorry for this, my love.
Just kill Viktor and me.
Aren't you allergic to traitors?
And you're trigger-happy, right?
Where's your courage?
You really are a shameless woman.
I would love to shave your head!
Remember this until the afterlife.
I will never let your soul rest.
Remember that!
So I crossed from one safe house
to another,
until I got here.
To be honest,
I never really planned
on bringing you along.
Who knows? I might survive.
And you have no idea how excited I am
And
it's a plus that I get to work
with my master Mikoy again.
and that's what we need to focus on.
Her hideout is too well-hidden
and too private.
The area also has limited entry points.
I believe this is where
Los Bandidos entered.
There isn't a place
where she can't hear us.
You thought I was dead?
I've memorized your every move.
Let's see if you can fight in the dark.
Show me your cat-like abilities.
Let's go. You stay here.
All right.
Go ahead. I'll take care of things here.
As if I would.
Support Chiara. We'll cover you.
You talk too much!
In Tagalog, One bullet is all it takes.
Mikoy.
This is my fight.
Hey, stop, or I will really kill you.
Mikoy, don't!
We coordinated
with the Italian authorities.
But for now, they are being silent.
But most of them got caught
or are on the run.
So is it safe to say that we successfully
destroyed the Concordat?
Where is Mikoy and Chiara?
Catching a fish is not the only thing
you can learn from Chiara.
But also catching Mikoy's heart.
Well, you know,
sometimes boring is better.
Think about the things
we've experienced this year.
I've had enough of action
and adventure, sweetheart.
All I wanted is a boring life.
That's all.